<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Index on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Index on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/seasonals/analytical-write-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/seasonals/analytical-write-up/</guid><description>Seasonal 3 2023 - Analytical; Linux Easy echo &amp;#34;${box-ip} analytical.htb&amp;#34; | sudo tee -a /etc/hosts Recon with nmap nmap -sCV analytical.htb Shows the following ports to be open; 22/tcp 80/tcp This tells me we need to use the browser, so off we go. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple site with a login option.
The login menu is actually pointing to data.analytical.htb, which is leads to a 404. So we need to add that one to our hosts file as well.</description></item><item><title/><link>/seasonals/drive-write-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/seasonals/drive-write-up/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>/seasonals/manager-write-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/seasonals/manager-write-up/</guid><description>Open Beta Season III: Manager Boxname Manager OS Windows Difficulty according the HTB Medium Difficulty for newbies like myself Hard Setup echo &amp;quot;${target-ip} manager.htb&amp;quot; | sudo tee -a /etc/hosts
Initial Recon nmap -sCV manager.htb gives you more information, mainly that we&amp;rsquo;re dealing with an IIS server, which we will be checking. We also have a DNS server, Domain Controller, SQL server and some other fun ports open.
┌─[eu-dedivip-2]─[10.10.14.66]─[htb-moonwitch@htb-iqv6bfvlz5]─[~] └──╼ [★]$ nmap -sCV manager.</description></item><item><title/><link>/seasonals/visual-write-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/seasonals/visual-write-up/</guid><description>Write-Up: Visual OS -&amp;gt; Windows Level -&amp;gt; Medium
Handy tips I always enter the IP - hostname into my /etc/hosts, this is simply faster for me to type.
echo &amp;quot;${TARGET_IP} visual.htb&amp;quot; | sudo tee -a /etc/hosts
Initial recon Start off with nmap -sCV ${TARGET_IP} This gets you the results you need; there&amp;rsquo;s an opening, a web server running on tcp/80.
![nmap](./Visual Write-up.assets/image-20231006090740045.png)
Needless to say, we check that out.
Since I know it&amp;rsquo;s a site, I&amp;rsquo;ll go on and check the used stack with Wappalyzer; this tells me that we&amp;rsquo;re using</description></item><item><title/><link>/tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/team/</guid><description>Meet our team of TrackHackers!
Moonwitch (Kelly) DevOps Advocate with a focus on infrastructure as code. Specialized in Python scripting and passionate about Capture The Flag challenges.
Rival23 (Pieter) SecOps Specialist and Network Guru. Master of network intrusion detection and secure architecture.
MattyBoi (Matthias) Infra Engineer with a specialty in Intune. Handles everything related to infrastructure and cloud solutions.
M (Nick T) Workplace Specialist focusing on M365 and SharePoint. Ensures seamless collaboration and document management across the team.</description></item></channel></rss>